# Vincent Good

## **Industrial Engineer**

As an Industrial Engineer, I enjoy using my problem-solving ability and technical skills to tackle tasks head-on. My academic background, industrial placements, and work experience have given me the ability to assess a situation and adapt my approach accordingly in a high-stress environment. This also further developed my attention to detail, team management and interpersonal communication skills.

Having travelled to England, Southern Africa, and South-East Asia, I am accustomed to adapting to my surroundings and bringing a unique perspective to others. Africa is my continent, and I believe in helping grow it to its full potential.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

2020 - 2021

#### **Industrial Engineering Intern**

Vacation Work (4 weeks)

#### **Certus Engineering**

Performed a time study to gather data on employee performance. Analysed the data and presented it to my mentor. Implemented 5S.

2020 - 2020

#### **Industrial Engineering Intern**

Vacation Work (6 weeks)

# HouseZero - Prefabricated modular home fabricators

Designed the plan to move to a new facility, as well as partially designed the floor plan for the new facility.

2013 - 2016

### Substitute manager and waiter

Part Time

#### Toni's Fish & Chips Co.

Waited and was the substitute manager at a 54-seater restaurant.

#### **EDUCATION**

2016 - Present

#### **Bachelor of Industrial Engineering**

University of Pretoria

2011 - 2015

#### **National Senior Certificate**

Pretoria Boys High School



#### **INFORMATION**

(+27)79 887 2395 vincent.nick.good@gmail.com Pretoria, South Africa 16 February 1997

#### Skills



#### Information Technology

- Programming (Python, R)
- MySQL Database Service
- Power BI
- Microsoft Office suite
- Comfortable in Linux
- Anylogic: Simulation Modelling Software



#### Leadership

- Managed a restaurant alone regularly, in the absence of the manager
- House prefect at Pretoria Boys High School
- Tutored mathematics to school students
- Captain of the TuksUltimate Team



#### Interests

- Technology Across the board, from computers through materials and engineering
- Woodworking Have made and sold home décor items
- Travel Travelled to Europe, South East Asia and through Southern Africa
- Technology Across the board, from computers through materials and engineering
- Photography Have done commercial assignments